Watch Your Step
I see it!
Over there!
Camera! Sound! Everything ready?
My legend starts here!
Here in front of us is Cenancle Island!
With a top-class resort and cutting-edge city,
I couldn't think of a more exciting place to be!
It's no wonder so many corporations and famous brands have flocking here.
Celebrities throughout the world are registering in storms to build summer villas here,
on what is the most
sought-after island in the world—
My ass! Who wrote this cheeky garbage!?
We're here already?
Clarion better hurry.
No journalist will ever host her own variety show,
let alone become an actress,
with a crummy script like this—
Why did you jump off!? That mic was expensive!
You all right?
Isn't that...
That console is over twenty years old!
And what's up with that
gaming skill she's got going on.
Oh, she's an android.
Hey, redhead.
Code Zero. State your model and owner's name.
If she isn't reacting to the code,
she might be a black-market android.
I guess I'll snatch her for myself.
Hey, you. Code Zero.
Oh, hello. Do you mean me?
Sorry about that. People make that mistake all the time.
I'm human!
I-I know I might not look like it, though!
No, no. It's my fault.
Does that mean you happen to be a full-body...
Th-That's right! I am.
Thank goodness.
Some people have a hard time understanding.
I get mistaken for an illegal android occasionally.
Sorry, I know it's confusing.
But I really wanted to wear a swimsuit. It's been so long...
A full-body cyborg!
Intriguing!
That game of yours, I mean!
Monster Bash, on an old DSD!
When that game came out it was the highlight of my youth!
But this game is over twenty years old...
Oh.
I'm double sorry!
No worries. I'm just shocked to see someone playing an old hand-held
rather than a direct-link game in this day and age.
My doctor gave it to me as part of my rehabilitation.
Intriguing.
But never mind that...
You took your time, didn't you? What'd you find?
I picked this up along the way.
Th-Thank you so much...
What about results?
Results?
Why must you always be so vague, Uzal?
I mean, did you find anything constructive?
Nothing.
They're still clean, right?
C-C-Cute!
Is this your daughter!?
Aren't you an amusing one!
We shall soon arrive at Cenancle Island.
All passengers, please prepare to disembark.
We still haven't introduced ourselves.
I'm Uzal Delilah.
The Compatible One
- Adepter -
#.01
The Compatible One
- Adepter -
#.01
I run a small business on Cenancle Island.
It's nice to meet you, Uzal.
I'm Nanakorobi Nene.
I'm moving to this island today.
Nice to meet you, Nene.
Hmm, "Nanakorobi"?
Uzal has designated me as Clarion.
I am her prized pet.
Side note: anyone who touches these ears goes to hell.
Awestruck
I wanna squeeze you! Till you explode!
Permission denied!
Feel free, to your heart's content.
Just let it happen, Clarion.
Clarion!
Heavy
Huh?
Careful. She's heavier than she looks.
She's the same as you.
The same?
She's another... full-body cyborg?
Touch my ears and
I'll kill you...
This is the first time... I've met someone like me!
Amazing! Please be my friend!
Your body is so cute! No fair!
I'm so envious!
Couldn't you have chosen an appearance you like, too?
This appearance is the result of
a simulation of how I would have looked.
My Mom and Dad gave me this face.
Oh, there's nothing wrong with that.
Your parents, huh? I think I...
I'll tell you what, Nene,
you can cling to Clarion as much as you want.
If you insist!
Don't go bucking, Clarion.
Watch the ears!
Squeezie, squeeze.
By the way, Nene.
What are your plans when you arrive? Something you need to do?
Well, um...
I'm here because my aunt will be taking care of me.
Is that so?
Korobase, eh?
I'm hoping to learn about the world
while I try to repay my aunt for her generosity.
Let's change the question.
If you got your hands on a bunch of money,
and you could obtain any one thing you wanted,
what would it be?
Something I want...
Excluding Clarion.
Um... If I can include my dreams, one thing comes to mind.
It's a bit complex, though.
If you wanted to buy it,
you would probably need a lot of money.
What's that?
World peace!
How fascinating! I can't get enough of you!
Go get some sleep, and think of something else.
And set Clarion free.
When I opened my eyes for the first time as a cyborg,
I was relieved that the world still looked beautiful.
And then I happened upon the idea of it...
Sorry, it's a little difficult to put into words.
Don't worry, I think it's
a surprisingly realistic dream.
You've got my vote.
Work hard to make it come true.
I will!
You should have everything you need to find me.
Once you've settled in, be sure to come visit.
And I'll get to see Clarion again!
No doubt.
Sorry to cut this short, Nene,
but something urgent has come up.
I need to get going.
Oh, of course.
Whoops, I nearly forgot.
Welcome to Cenancle Island!
Thank you!
Say hi to Korobase for me.
Yes, ma'am! And see you later, Clarion!
Nanakorobi Nene.
Hard to believe that's an authorized first-generation.
No wonder Korobase is proud of her.
Hold on. How did she know my aunt's name?
Eh, who cares.
Hey, this is Nene. I'm at the harbor.
Don't worry, I know the address.
Yes. I'll be fine, really.
Aunt Takumi
A brand new place. Brand new smells.
The first time I've met someone like me.
I hope we can be friends.
Even the weather's nice!
Dad, Mom, I feel truly welcome for once!
From now on, I...
What? But that way...
Uzal...
Clarion!
Dad, Mom...
I need to get...
to my friends!
Clarion!
Uzal! Clarion!
There they are!
But they're running towards it?
I can go for about an hour without oxygen.
World peace! Hell, yeah!
Hey fools, I'm back.
What the hell's the meaning of this, Sahar Schehera?
You activated BUER, didn't you?
You bet we did.
And it went berserk, didn't it?
You knew it was defective!?
The entire underground facility has collapsed!
The organization is in shambles!
Because you started it up on your own, you moron.
Moron.
That activation key's a dummy.
The real one's on me.
Did you expect me not to notice this little rebellion of yours behind my back?
How could you do this!?
It even damaged the surface!
Demon!
Fiend!
And you made us wear these clothes too!
Isn't this your own fault for betraying me?
Hand over the real activation key!
Settle down, small fries.
Aren't you all trapped down there?
Shouldn't you be begging me to save you?
Can it!
Look at this mess...
Guess I didn't give them enough paid holidays.
You mean a reason to like you.
Shut up.
All right, Clarion. Pandora Device, open.
Owner's consent, confirmed. Acknowledged.
Release skill, Elpis Series.
Anti Material and Close Quarters Combat.
Uzal! Clarin!
Clarin?
Mutilate
Mangle
Clarin?
Don't shorten it.
Surround her!
Pincer attack!
Amazing...
Is she another one of Sahar's puppets?
Let's crush her.
Loading the rock drill cartridge!
Make Nene's protection top priority!
FOR ELIMINATION
Clarin!
This way, Nene.
Hey! We're withdrawing, Clario!
Clario
Don't shorten it.
The transmission!
A smoke screen, seriously!?
Clarin!
Forgive me, Clarin!
Don't worry about her.
She's just mad that a mere
excavation bot shortened her arm,
Humiliation
Grr
or perhaps even madder we're doing the same to her name.
Humiliation
Grr
An arm or two's nothing to fuss about.
Just because it's a prosthetic doesn't make it okay!
Well, it was destroyed protecting you,
so I doubt she even minds.
Anyway, Nene. What are you doing here?
Oh, that's right!
We need to get out of here!
Look what's happening to the city!
I'd love to, hun, but they're blocking our escape.
What are those things?
Bad guys! Criminals!
That's what makes this an emergency.
Perhaps you could help me?
Of course! I'll do anything if it'll help!
Nothing much, I need to write a little data to your body's storage, okay?
There's a very complicated reason for this...
Yes, ma'am! Write away!
Be a little warier of others.
My, oh my...
Hey, Clarin.
Don't shorten it.
We're going to give Nanakorobi Nene
temporary authority to use the Pandora Device.
You're kidding...
Yes. That's the look I taught you, but not quite the right words.
What's a Pandora—
Stick those fingers of yours in here.
My heart can't take this!
I-I'm not into this kind of stuff, uh...
All jokes aside, you need to do this.
Guide her hand, Clarion.
You can connect via your F port, correct?
Y-Yes, but hold on!
Pandora Device, open!
Release skill, Elpis Series. Advanced Firearms!
Deep inside me, where I can't reach...
Not far from there...
I feel something coming inside me!
Behead—
Behold!
The scene in front of us is from Vulcan City on Cenancle Island.
The ground around us is rumbling,
and there are explosions everywhere.
This nearly dangerous report is coming to you live by none other than me, Vlind—
Where's Sahar!?
Get us out of here!
I'm working on it!
I found them!
They're coming!
Left!
I won't let you hurt Clarin again! So there!
What do we do?
There's nothing you can do with these shitty things!
I'm rounding up all the security bots I can find.
Thank you for protecting Clarion.
We think you deserve a reward.
Here.
Oh!
Thank you, Clarin!
Use that to protect us.
But I've spent all this time in rehabilitation.
I've never even touched a gun!
Huh?
Well done.
This isn't my usual cyborg OS.
The application we just installed to you is integrating with your current OS.
It's finished starting up.
Whoa, some other things appeared!
I brought all I could find!
Restrain them!
Just as I thought.
She's an adepter.
The "full-body cyborg" is a technology still in development.
After rigorous rehabilitation, cyborgs are eventually able to handle more difficult movements.
But many people have trouble adapting to the prosthetics.
It will most likely be many years before the technology becomes commonplace.
However, there have been reports of extremely rare cases
where people learn to use their
prosthetics the same as, or rather,
even better than a real body.
Reports are scarce, even globally,
but these "adepters" compensate for the limits of their prosthetic technology
with their own innate abilities and talents.
The info is kept under wraps, but it's known that they are mostly teenagers or younger.
To think we'd happen upon one...
It's an application that aids in
skill-based prosthetics control.
That's what we installed on you.
Another magazine.
It's only temporary, but it has given you the shooting skill of a fully trained professional.
It was essentially designed for humanoid robots,
but you handled it just fine.
I can do something like that?
Look out, here comes more!
It's true...
They seem slow to me, just like before.
I know exactly what to do!
Seconds
Huh? I don't remember anymore...
It's a temporary supplement,
to keep it out of mischievous hands.
What does this do? Whoops!
Development on it has been shelved,
since it violates about a dozen international laws.
Never mind that!
Clarin!
Were you hurt!?
You're all burnt!
Clarion's fine, but what about yourself?
Yes, ma'am! I'm as good as ever!
I forgot! I need to call my aunt!
Aunt Takumi
Oh no, I can't get through.
Don't worry about Korobase.
Huh?
Korobase Takumi, right?
That's right! Uzal, do you know my aunt?
Believe it or not, we're close friends!
Oh, so that's why!
Well, let's get somewhere safe.
Uzal. Nene's awake.
Clarin!
Why am I naked!?
Clarin, you naughty little girl.
Simpleminded girl...
You collapsed all of a sudden, so we brought you here.
I collapsed?
That's weird.
That's never happened before.
Where are we?
My lab.
It's like my old hospital ward.
Are you a doctor, Uzal?
Sort of.
Uzal, we're out of time.
I-I'm fine, so please repair Clarin's arm first!
Of course. Well, I'd love to, but...
Sahar! Get out here!
Sahar?
The bad guys have found us!
If you won't open the door...
The wall!
We're in a fix!
Clarion! Pandora Device, open!
You know the procedure by now, right Nene?
Y-Yes!
But are you sure Clarion doesn't mind?
There! Just a little more!
Yeah!
I'm fine.
Do it, Nene! It's for world peace!
All right!
Then...
It's coming into me again...
Huh? This feels different than before...
What's this supposed to be!?
It's a camouflage under development that I thought you could use.
Camouflage?
I integrated it inside of you, in a way.
Integrated?
Isn't it natural to hide your identity when you're up to something top secret?
Top secret!? What's that supposed to mean!?
This is the opposite of camouflage!
I have weapons ready for you over there.
Take your pick, honey!
Clarin, stand back!
I heard you, but I refuse.
Huh?
Save us, Mistress Sahar!
Sigh
We can't take any more!
BUER won't stop!
Sigh
It just keeps rampaging!
The stop code won't work either!
It's going to bore straight through the base of the island at this rate.
Forgive us, Mistress Sahar!
Don't call me that name.
All right, fine.
I'll stop it, okay?
You know them? Sahar? BUER?
Nene.
You were saying you'd like to buy world peace.
For starters, would you like to try buying peace for this island?
Huh?
PANDORA IN THE CRIMSON SHELL
Accessing the device named nature
Infinite answers to the synopsis found
read
write
enter
code
to
ol
no
ou
shuu
Sharing tools can lead to unavoidable situations
PANDORADIO
TRANSMITTED SOMEHOW
Nice to meet you, Clarin!
I hope we'll work well together!
I never authorized that form of address.
Come on, it's so nice and cute.
Clarin.
Disconnect me.
Saving data
Strengthening predictions
Even my latest updates
can't help explain why you're so nice to me
error
Error error
parameter
Please help me understand
shou
tai
wa
na
ni
where these emotions came from
Find me at the end of this labrynth
of feelings I can no longer control
I understand the concept of emotions
shii
but I can't make any sense of my own
I want to pull out these cords
and head straight to you
I won't come to understand love
without having you here with me
Clarin! Clarin!
What's that big black ball that's underground?
A boring machine.
I wonder if I could get a ball that big rolling.
Deep Underground
- Geofront -
Boring, not bowling.